

PROFILE

Born in Cyprus, 21 years old computer enthusiast.

2 Years' experience in Java. 2 Years' experience in C++.

1 Year experience in C#.

4 Video Game Projects in Unity.

1 Video Game Project in Unreal

Engine.

Fundamental Web Development and MySQL knowledge.

Worked at a company and designed a professional website at the age of 15

Active person with passion in Drumming and Music.

Fluent in Greek and English, very skilled at communicating and developing relationships in the workplace.

My goal is to work on large projects at local and/or international companies and create life-changing video games.

CONTACT

PHONE: +35799920132

EMAIL:

Kouis16cy@gmail.com

WEBSITE/PORTFOLIO:

www.nikolaskouis.com

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nikolas-kouis-041568229/

HOBBIES

Drumming
Gaming
Game Development

NIKOLAOS KOUIS

EDUCATION

Institution: Linopetra Lyceum

Field: Physical Sciences and Computer Science

Dates: From 2016 to 2019

Institution: Essex University

Course: BSc - Computer Science, Year 2

Dates: From 2020 to 2023

WORK EXPERIENCE

QS Lysis - Web Designer

2016-2018

Designer the official and professional website of the company.

KIK Trading – Mini Mall Stores (MMS)

2021-2021

Summer job as a cashier in MMS in Limassol.

Amdocs - Vubiquity

2022-2022

Software Engineering Intern.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Pancyprian Discus Throwing Competition Participant
- Drumming Grade 6
- Duke of Edinburgh's International Award Bronze Course
- Computer IGCSEs Mathematics IGCSEs First Language Pearson Edexcel - Second Language Cambridge
- Unity Unreal Engine Projects
- Website Designer
- The Loop: Ouroboros, Horror Game, currently on Alpha, using Unreal Engine.
- Ritualist, Horror Game, currently on Alpha, on Unity using C#.
- Surveillance Job, published Android puzzle game, using Unity.
- **Joined the Global Game Jam 2022**, Horror game on Unity using C#, Finished game.
- **Joined the Brackeys Game Jam 2022**, Horror Shooter VR Game on Unity using C#, Finished game.
- Won the Essex Game Development Society Game Jam 2022, First Person game, using Unity.
- Joined the Amdocs Hackathon 2022, Web based Platform game, Finished game.